No fever.
Normal pulse, too.
Then don't tell me...
Did your company go under?!
It did not.
Did you kill some—
I did not.
Then why would you do something like that?
You mean invite you to my house?
You must have a reason.
I felt like it?
Liar!
So, you really just want to hang out?
You never do things because you "feel like it"!
Yes, really.
Great. I'll go.
Okay. When works for you?
How about... Sunday?
Okay!
Now that's settled, time to plan!
This has gotten fun.
Oh, how about I bring something to snack on?
What would you like?
Yes! I'd like something pricey.
I'm asking Neiru.
Maybe I'll bring a takoyaki maker.
Forget that junk for now.
"Junk"?
Just listen.
Oh, does Sunday work for you?
Oh, that might be nice!
Yeah.
Hey, what about you two?
Of course it's fine.
I wouldn't miss it.
This is a recording of President Aonuma's dreams.
Using the technology developed here,
it is possible to analyze brainwaves
and convert the subject's dreams to video.
Whoa.
They're not dreams, though.
But they're not reality either.
Science is amazing.
The picture is still rough and monochrome,
Ai, have her record you.
We'll get a sexy fantasy out of it.
but with more research, it will
one day be clear and in full color.
Don't lump me in with you.
I can't believe you live at your company.
This feels like a field trip.
Who are you, anyway, Neiru?
What an existentialist question.
What's that?
Are you familiar with a group called Plati?
Yes. I heard only people with really high IQs can join.
Ms. Neiru is a member of Japan Plati.
Wow. I knew you were really smart.
I'm just good at thinking logically.
How modest, ma'am.
I was born via artificial insemination of a member.
Oh, so that's why you said you never had parents.
For real? They won't tell you who your parents are?
There'd be no point. It was just a pairing.
That puts my worries in perspective.
We've reached floor B9.
This is our medical floor.
Are you a doctor too, Neiru?
No. I'm not in charge of this floor.
I'm just filling in for now.
Hey, are we there yet?
Here.
Whoa.
Well then, excuse me.
Yes. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
All right! This is your room, Neiru?
Whoa, books galore.
Hey, Neiru,
what's this guy's name?
Adam.
Can I touch him?
Sure.
Clean up all this paper.
Come here.
Where should we eat?
Oh, wait a moment.
I've got exams next week.
I haven't studied at all.
Me, too.
You're lucky, Neiru.
You get to run this huge company.
It's like we live in different worlds.
I...
Anyway, Rika, isn't it about time?
All right, let's get started!
Yesterday, Rika and I got worked
up talking about fun things to do.
It's a pretty color.
Well?
Grown-up, right?
We thought we could all do our nails and stuff.
Ever painted them?
Nope.
I'll do Neiru's.
Show me your hands.
No.
You have pretty nails.
Don't worry. I won't screw up!
Huh? Do I really?
You're good, Momo.
You could go pro.
I wonder.
But I think I'd like to be a dietitian.
I'm thinking of going to school for it.
Wow. I'm impressed you're thinking about that stuff.
I want to go abroad.
Wouldn't working in English be cool?
Then an international marriage to a hot guy.
What a surprise.
I wonder where I want to go.
Hang on, we're not talking about vacation.
Oh, but I might want to try living on my own.
Oh, I get that.
That's a dream of mine, too.
There. All done.
One's a different color.
We match.
And you, Neiru?
What's your dream?
Oh yeah, you haven't told us yet.
I guess we're all sharing our dreams now.
I think I'll probably stay like this forever.
Huh?
Come on, I didn't mean that earlier.
You don't have to run a company your whole life.
Oh, if you like books, why not become a writer?
Let me introduce a friend.
I want you to meet her.
Your friend?
Someone's inside.
She was born at Japan Plati like I was.
Awano Kotobuki.
Kotobuki.
Adam is her pet.
Her hair color...
She's albino.
She's gorgeous.
Albinos are said to bring good
fortune to those around them.
Kotobuki was always cheerful and optimistic.
She'd tell me to "really enjoy myself."
"Was"?
Isn't she just sleeping?
She's in a vegetative state.
Huh?
Kotobuki was a doctor of psychiatry.
She was scientifically analyzing the mysteries of life.
Death, in particular.
She performed near-death experiments,
and eventually didn't come back.
Near-death experiments...
Scientists try to solve difficult problems. It's in their nature.
She was your friend, wasn't she?
Yes. I met Kotobuki in a dream.
A dream?
An Egg dream.
He's incredible.
He's Pinky.
Is he a type of corn snake?
Who knows?
It's been a long time, Neiru.
Kotobuki...
Is Adam well?
Yes. You look well, too.
I guess. I'm not bored.
Still, I'm glad.
I get a chance to say goodbye to you.
I'd better thank God.
We're not children of God, remember?
Scientists who can't believe in God are incompetent.
I'm not a scientist at all.
You know that.
Of course. Just needling you.
You'll protect me, right?
Or do you want me to protect you?
Oh, that's nice. What a lovely weapon.
Let's really enjoy ourselves.
There you are!
Pinky!
What's that? It's hilarious!
Faster! Faster!
They'll catch us if we don't hurry.
Kotobuki, why did you die?
Why couldn't you come back?
When adrenaline enters the brain,
they say you see a field of flowers
to overcome the fear of death.
I wanted to pick one and bring it back to you.
This isn't funny!
I won't forgive any more jokes.
The me in the world you're in did die.
But that allowed me to experience it.
I was right, Neiru: Parallel worlds do exist!
The possibility of worlds that might have been.
It was your favorite genre of fiction.
Yes! Our parallel selves are alive!
That's nice, but I can't see you ever again.
Being satisfied with seeing each other is so commonplace.
We're not some couple that can't handle long-distance.
I can't be so philosophical about it yet.
At stage four Thanato, there was a sweet smell like honey.
I felt like an insect preyed upon by a carnivorous plant.
The temptation of death?
Not so much "temptation."
More like my mind and body were abducted.
Abducted? By what?
By innocent sorrow.
What chatty guinea pigs you are!
Ow. That hurt.
Where's Pinky?
Back in my pendant.
Don't worry. He'll regenerate soon.
I see.
I won't give up.
No matter what it takes, I'll go to the place where you died
and bring your statue back to—
You can't envision dying.
You can't reach an abstract place.
Then I'll use near-death experiments, too.
Don't be ridiculous.
If you went to that zone, you'd die, too.
What would happen to me in reality then?
Where did you go?!
You must know.
The government will come for my body someday.
I won't let them do that.
It's just a container.
But I was attached to it in my own way.
I don't want adults touching it.
I know.
Then you must know what I want you to do.
I don't.
Stop that.
I know you're not that dense.
Why?
Why are you always so selfish?
In the end, you left me to deal with everything!
Won't you praise my original research methods?
You don't consider other people's feelings at all!
You're used to that.
It's still not normal to just die!
Isn't abnormality more fun?
It's not fun for me!
Look at your face.
It's fine. You made new friends, right?
How did...
You're softer than you used to be.
But they're not like us.
You made connections with people.
That's a wonderful thing.
Treasure them.
You aren't there.
I'll make friends with those girls in another world-line.
I finally caught you, you cocky brat.
Kotobuki,
Ow, ow, ow.
I won't be satisfied until I cut open your pretty little chest.
Who are you?!
Well, Kotobuki,
I'm Doctor Seki! You stole my job
as chief of the medical center!
I'll analyze every micron of your body
and return to those glorious days!
Huh?
Oh, the guy who was obsessed with my body.
So, this is my trauma.
It's true that he's the last person I'd want to dissect me.
True.
What?!
Fools!
I'm the world-famous Seki!
I have numerous doctorates! My
papers have been published in Future!
I've been on the cover of Future.
Me too.
Ha! I won't accept it!
If that's true, solve this problem.
It's ultra-difficult, with a zero-percent success rate!
Find the radius of a circle that
intersects points A, B, C, and D.
Only a genius can solve it.
I'm going to do it.
So will I.
You little brats could never figure it out!
I'm going to blow your mind!
Then answer!
The answer is
there is no such circle!
Huh? It can't be.
These little girls solved a problem
not even I could? In seconds?
No need.
Doctor what's-his-name had pride, if nothing else.
Pride chicken.
Was it that funny?
You sounded like a friend of mine.
Bravo.
Take care of the me in reality.
All right.
What should you do? Say it in words.
Why?
Because you always do what you say you will.
I'll disconnect your life support.
Good. Sorry for a lot.
You should be.
Thank you.
Kotobuki was in an Egg?
Yes. There can't even be a miracle now.
Kotobuki is dead.
Still, you're not even related. You can't just...
I know.
But if I delay, the government will come for her.
An albino genius is a valuable sample.
A sample...
But that's just an excuse!
Can you kill a girl like her for that?
She looks alive. Like she's just sleeping.
She's already dead.
Just a container.
Sorry, but I can't watch.
It's different from killing Seeno Evils or Haters there.
Yeah! This is for real.
That's too much, even if she did ask you.
I can't believe you're just going to do it.
Then just go home.
I didn't ask you to take a field trip here.
You shouldn't say it like that.
We're worried, too.
About what?
I mean, you're our friend.
If you do that, you might end up
with trauma, or baggage, or...
There's no problem, then.
I won't get sentimental about
stopping a dead person's respiration.
Oh, is that so?
Being smart is scary.
I'm more frightened of others' overheated passions.
Are you talking about me?! Are you?!
Huh!? Hey!
Stop it, everyone.
Kotobuki can hear you.
Hey. That's normal human sentimentality, right?
Worrying she might hear us.
Ridiculous.
Anyway, Neiru, you should at least sleep on it.
I'm going back after all.
Hey, Ai!
Ai can get close to her.
She might have better luck changing Neiru's mind alone.
Well, I guess.
It seems like Neiru's being stubborn.
Ai might get through.
President Aonuma is getting closer
to the truth behind the temptation of death.
Kotobuki did give her a hint.
Innocent sorrow.
You managed to deflect her with an excuse, though.
Girls' suicides.
If we told them the real reason, none of them would fight.
Yeah. Not if they knew the root cause is the two of us.
Do you think so?
I think they would actually fight against you.
Because they're girls, they understand girls' sorrows.
What? What's going on?
She's connected to Acca and Ura-Acca, too?
You came to stop me?
I want to hear about Kotobuki.
I see.
What else did Kotobuki say?
What else?
Why did she want you to do that for her?
She doesn't want adults to touch her.
See? If you'd told us that, the others
would have been more understanding.
Really?
Yeah.
You're not very upfront, Neiru.
I really... tried to push it,
but my fingers shook.
Yeah.
One time, Koito and I tried fortune-telling using Kokkuri.
We asked if Koito's crush liked her back.
I think it was probably Mr. Sawaki.
Yeah.
The coin landed on "yes."
I didn't move it, so I thought Koito did,
but she seemed really happy.
I wondered if she'd be that happy if she'd moved it herself.
Maybe I moved it without knowing, to make Koito happy.
But... I really don't know.
That's what fantasy is.
Yeah.
With two of us...
It's fantasy.
Kotobuki's body was scheduled
for collection tomorrow morning.
Yeah.
Did you want something done before that?
It was you who made Neiru's
Wonder Egg Kotobuki, wasn't it?
Just a coincidence.
Thank you.
"It is the hour to be drunken!
Be drunken, if you would not be martyred slaves of Time;
be drunken continually!
With wine, with poetry, or with virtue, as you will."
Let's really enjoy ourselves.
We only live once.
To be continued.